http://www.electropages.com/privacy-policy

| Test & Measurement
ToF distance and motion sensor modules include infrared laser light source
| Semiconductors
New intelligent revolution eBook explores role of AI in public safety
07-12-2020
| New Technologies
View all Mouser Electronics news
RS Components
Extensive range of laboratory equipment for all forms of work
10-12-2020
| Subs & Systems
Extensive range of circuit protection and EMI design kits for engineers
08-12-2020
| Subs & Systems
Condition monitoring sensors detect multiple physical variables
04-12-2020
| Test & Measurement
Extensive range of handheld test and measurement instruments
01-12-2020
| Subs & Systems
View all RS Components news
TTI Europe
Portable label printer offers a combination of ability, print quality and speed
| Connectors, Switches & EMECH
Low profile MiMo Wi-Fi antenna in an ultra-low-profile package
Microchip Technology
FPGA available in engineering silicon and headed for space qualification
| Semiconductors
Safety certified capacitive touchscreen controller family for the home appliance market
18-11-2020
| Semiconductors
Cryptographic companion device brings pre-programmed security to the automotive market
12-11-2020
| Automotive Technologies
View all Microchip Technology news
Texas Instruments
Ultra-precise current sense amplifiers in a compact footprint
06-08-2020
| Power
Non-synchronous boost controller suitable for automotive applications
05-08-2020
| Semiconductors
Automotive reinforced isolated delta-sigma modulator for voltage sensing
04-08-2020
| Automotive Technologies
General-purpose mux offers an internal injection current control feature
03-08-2020
| Connectors, Switches & EMECH
View all Texas Instruments news
ROHM Semiconductor
Reducing laser circuit design load while improving distance measurement accuracy
| Automotive Technologies
New automotive primary DC-DC converters ensuring stable operation
13-11-2020
| Power
Reducing the size of automotive designs with ultra-compact MOSFETs
09-11-2020
| Automotive Technologies
View all ROHM Semiconductor news
Analog Devices
Quadband VCOs offer wideband ability without compromising phase noise performance
09-12-2020
| Power
Alias-free ADC that enables increased functionality and ease of use
30-11-2020
| Semiconductors
Two-channel power system managers minimise supply disturbances
09-10-2020
| Power
DACs for industrial automation and process control applications
Effective from: 07 June 2018
Electropages Media is owned by Mouser Electronics, part of the Berkshire Hathaway group and contains Electropages, Electromaker and Zeta within it’s business structure.
This privacy policy details how Electropages Media use any information collected about you in the use of this website.
What information is collected about you
How the information will be used
Where the information is stored
Access to your information
Cookies
Other Websites
Changes to the policy
Contact Us
What information is collected about you
Information is collected about site users in multiple ways.
Firstly, in using the site. On visiting the site, log files will be stored by the Apache web server. The information stored in the log files contains:
IP address
Address of web page visited before user came to the site
User browser type
Date and time of any request the user makes on the site
User OS Information
Enquiry About Product form
Secondly, is upon entering data in a form on the site, such as Enquire About This Product.
In completing the form we collect:
Name
Email address
Comment
And may collect the following should it be filled in:
Job Title
Telephone
Company
Company Website
Country
Quantity (if interested in a specific number of product)
Electropages Newsletters
Thirdly, is enlisting for one or more newsletters that we offer. In signing up for a newsletter we will collect:
Email Address
If you decide to fill in further information to receive more personalised emails, we will also collect the additional information:
First Name
Surname
Job Role
Industry
Country
If you sign up for the Electropages General Product News you may receive emails from new distributors on the site. You will always have the option to manage and unsubscribe from any list or newsletter.
Hotjar
We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar's privacy policy by clicking on this link.
You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar's storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar's use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this opt-out link.
How the information will be used
The apache web server log files known as error and success logs. These are used in order to manage the web server. The log files give feedback about the activity and performance of the server as well as any problems that may be occurring.
If errors occur, these will be shown in the log files, making us aware if the server is not running at optimum efficiency and helping us address any issues in a timely manner. The information is only used for these purposes and the log files are accessible on the server by particular users. They are stored for a period of 6 months.
Enquiry About Product form
If the ‘Enquire about this Product’ form is completed, the information is sent to both Electropages Media in addition to the supplier whose product page you visited.
If there is no supplier then the information will just be sent to Electropages.
This information will only be used to contact you regarding the product you have enquired about. It will not be added to any newsletters or marketing emails.
If you tick the box for the option to have your contact details stored to enable pre-population of the forms, then your name and email will be stored in a cookie on your machine only. This data will only be used to pre-fill the ‘Enquire about this Product’ contact forms.
Electropages Newsletters
If you sign up for one or more of the newsletters from Electropages then the information you have entered will be stored with Send in Blue (sendinblue.com). This website allows newsletters and Electronics News articles to be scheduled and managed securely.
The information you enter will only ever be used to send you the newsletters you have requested and you are able to manage your subscriptions at any time by visiting the website.
Contacting Electropages
By emailing us directly we will only ever use the information sent to us to contact you regarding your query. We will not add your contact details to any newsletter list.
Hotjar
Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience and this enables us to build, maintain and improve our service. This data will not be used for any other purpose.
Where the information is stored
The website is hosted using Rackspace Cloud servers, so the log files will be held securely on the server running the Electropages site.
Enquiry About Product form
The information relating to product enquiries in addition to direct email enquiries (at Electropages and also the supplier), is stored on our server in order for us to manage the enquiries as efficiently as possible.
Electropages Newsletters
In subscribing to any of the Electropages newsletters the information will be stored in sendinblue. The information is stored securely on their servers and only used to send newsletters that you have requested.
Access to your information
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your information please contact us.
If you have made a mistake or wish to unsubscribe from any newsletters that you receive from us, please either manage your subscriptions or email us and we will be happy to help you.
Cookies
Cookies are tiny data files stored in your web browser when you visit a website. They allow websites to recognise and store small pieces of information in the web browser, such as analytics, preferences and others items. These help the website provide functionality and on occasion, personalised content.
Cookies may be stored directly by a website that you visit (“first-party cookies”) or by third-party services that the website uses for additional functionality (“third-party cookies”).
Please read our full cookie policy.
Other Websites
This website may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website, so when viewing other sites please refer to their privacy policy for information on their data capture and storage.
Changes to the policy
We regularly review our privacy policy and will update this web page as necessary. This privacy policy was last updated February 2020.
Contact Us
Please contact us if you have any questions about this policy or information we may hold about you.
By email: info@electropages.com
By phone: +44 (0)1202 237137
In writing to: Electropages Media Ltd, 3 Winchester Place, Poole, Dorset, BH15 1NX, United Kingdom
